<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="strings_azkar_translate1" translatable="false">We have reached the morning and at this very time unto Allah belongs all sovereignty, and all praise is for Allah. None has the right to be worshipped except Allah, alone, without partner, to Him belongs all sovereignty and praise and He is over all things omnipotent. My Lord, I ask You for the good of this day and the good of what follows it and I take refuge in You from the evil of this day and the evil of what follows it. My Lord, I take refuge in You from laziness and senility. My Lord, I take refuge in You from torment in the Fire and punishment in the grave.</string>
    <string name="strings_azkar_translate2" translatable="false">O Allah, by your leave we have reached the morning and by Your leave we have reached the evening, by Your leave we live and die and unto You is our resurrection.</string>
    <string name="strings_azkar_translate3" translatable="false">O Allah, You are my Lord, none has the right to be worshipped except You, You created me and I am Your servant and I abide to Your covenant and promise as best I can, I take refuge in You from the evil of which I have committed. I acknowledge Your favour upon me and I acknowledge my sin, so forgive me, for verily none can forgive sin except You.</string>
    <string name="strings_azkar_translate4" translatable="false">O Allah, verily I have reached the morning and call on You, the bearers of Your throne, Your angles, and all of Your creation to witness that You are Allah, none has the right to be worshipped except You, alone, without partner and that Muhammad is Your Servant and Messenger (four times).</string>
    <string name="strings_azkar_translate5" translatable="false">O Allah, what blessing I or any of Your creation have risen upon, is from You alone, without partner, so for You is all praise and unto You all thanks.</string>
    <string name="strings_azkar_translate6" translatable="false">O Allah, grant my body health, O Allah, grant my hearing health, O Allah, grant my sight health. None has the right to be worshipped except You (three times) </string>
    <string name="strings_azkar_translate7" translatable="false">Allah is Sufficient for me, none has the right to be worshipped except Him, upon Him I rely and He is Lord of the exalted throne. (seven times morning and evening)</string>
    <string name="strings_azkar_translate8" translatable="false">I take refuge in Allah\'s perfect words from the evil He has created. (three times in the evening)</string>
    <string name="strings_azkar_translate9" translatable="false">O Allah, I ask You for pardon and well-being in this life and the next. O Allah, I ask You for pardon and well-being in my religious and worldly affairs, and my family and my wealth. O Allah, veil my weaknesses and set at ease my dismay. O Allah, preserve me from the front and from behind and on my right and on my left and from above, and I take refuge with You lest I be swallowed up by the earth.</string>
    <string name="strings_azkar_translate10" translatable="false">O Allah, Knower of the unseen and the seen, Creator of the heavens and the Earth, Lord and Sovereign of all things, I bear witness that none has the right to be worshipped except You. I take refuge in You from the evil of my soul and from the evil and shirk of the devil, and from committing wrong against my soul or bringing such upon another Muslim.</string>
    <string name="strings_azkar_translate11" translatable="false">In the name of Allah with whose name nothing is harmed on earth nor in the heavens and He is The All-Seeing, The All-Knowing. (three times) </string>
    <string name="strings_azkar_translate12" translatable="false">I am pleased with Allah as a Lord, and Islam as a religion and Muhammad peace be upon to him as a Prophet. (three times)</string>
    <string name="strings_azkar_translate13" translatable="false">How perfect Allah is and I praise Him by the number of His creation and His pleasure, and by the weight of His throne, and the ink of His words. (three times) </string>
    <string name="strings_azkar_translate14" translatable="false">How perfect Allah is and I praise Him. (one hundred times)</string>
    <string name="strings_azkar_translate15" translatable="false">O Ever Living, O Self-Subsisting and Supporter of all, by Your mercy I seek assistance, rectify for me all of my affairs and do not leave me to myself, even for the blink of an eye.</string>
    <string name="strings_azkar_translate16" translatable="false">None has the right to be worshipped except Allah, alone, without partner, to Him belongs all sovereignty and praise, and He is over all things omnipotent. (one hundred times)</string>
    <string name="strings_azkar_translate17" translatable="false">We have reached the morning and at this very time all sovereignty belongs to Allah, Lord of the worlds. O Allah, I ask You for the good of this day, its triumphs and its victories, its light and its blessings and its guidance, and I take refuge in You from the evil of this day and the evil that follows it.</string>
    <string name="strings_azkar_translate18" translatable="false">O Allah, | take refuge with You from disbelief and poverty, and | take refuge with You from the punishment of the grave. None has the right to be worshipped except You. (three times)</string>
    <string name="strings_azkar_translate19" translatable="false">We have reached the evening and at this very time unto Allah belongs all sovereignty, and all praise is for Allah. None has the right to be worshipped except Allah, alone, without partner, to Him belongs all sovereignty and praise and He is over all things omnipotent. My Lord, I ask You for the good of this night and the good of what follows it and I take refuge in You from the evil of this night and the evil of what follows it. My Lord, I take refuge in You from laziness and senility. My Lord, I take refuge in You from torment in the Fire and punishment in the grave.</string>
    <string name="strings_azkar_translate20" translatable="false">O Allah, by Your leave we have reached the evening and by Your leave we have reached the morning, by Your leave we live and die and unto You is our return.</string>
    <string name="strings_azkar_translate21" translatable="false">O Allah, You are my Lord, none has the right to be worshipped except You, You created me and I am Your servant and I abide to Your covenant and promise as best I can, I take refuge in You from the evil of which I have committed. I acknowledge Your favour upon me and I acknowledge my sin, so forgive me, for verily none can forgive sin except You.</string>
    <string name="strings_azkar_translate22" translatable="false">O Allah, verily I have reached the evening and call on You, the bearers Of Your throne, Your angles, and all of Your creation to witness that You are Allah, none has the right to be worshipped except You, alone, Without partner and that Muhammad is Your Servant and Messenger. (four times.)</string>
    <string name="strings_azkar_translate23" translatable="false">O Allah, what blessing I or any of Your creation have risen upon, is from You alone, without partner, so for You is all praise and unto You all thanks.</string>
    <string name="strings_azkar_translate24" translatable="false">O Allah, grant my body health, O Allah, grant my hearing health, O Allah, grant my sight health. None has the right to be worshipped except You.</string>
    <string name="strings_azkar_translate25" translatable="false">Allah is Sufficient for me, none has the right to be worshipped except Him, upon Him I rely and He is Lord of the exalted throne. (seven times morning and evening)</string>
    <string name="strings_azkar_translate26" translatable="false">I take refuge in Allah\'s perfect words from the evil He has created. (three times in the evening) </string>
    <string name="strings_azkar_translate27" translatable="false">O Allah, I ask You for pardon and well-being in this life and the next. O Allah, I ask You for pardon and well-being in my religious and worldly affairs, and my family and my wealth. O Allah, veil my weaknesses and set at ease my dismay. O Allah, preserve me from the front and from behind and on my right and on my left and from above, and I take refuge with You lest I be swallowed up by the earth.</string>
    <string name="strings_azkar_translate28" translatable="false">O Allah, Knower of the unseen and the seen, Creator of the heavens and the Earth, Lord and Sovereign of all things, I bear witness that none has the right to be worshipped except You. I take refuge in You from the evil of my soul and from the evil and shirk of the devil, and from committing wrong against my soul or bringing such upon another Muslim.</string>
    <string name="strings_azkar_translate29" translatable="false">In the name of Allah with whose name nothing is harmed on earth nor in the heavens and He is The All-Seeing, The All-Knowing. (three times)</string>
    <string name="strings_azkar_translate30" translatable="false">I am pleased with Allah as a Lord, and Islam as a religion and Muhammad peace be upon to him as a Prophet. (three times)</string>
    <string name="strings_azkar_translate31" translatable="false">How perfect Allah is and I praise Him by the number of His creation and His pleasure, and by the weight of His throne, and the ink of His words. (three times)</string>
    <string name="strings_azkar_translate32" translatable="false">How perfect Allah is and I praise Him. (one hundred times)</string>
    <string name="strings_azkar_translate33" translatable="false">O Ever Living, O Self-Subsisting and Supporter of all, by Your mercy I seek assistance, rectify for me all of my affairs and do not leave me to myself, even for the blink of an eye.</string>
    <string name="strings_azkar_translate34" translatable="false">O Allah, I take refuge with You from disbelief and poverty, and I take refuge with You from the punishment of the grave. None has the right to be worshipped except You. (three times) </string>


    <string name="strings_azkar_translate35" translatable="false">I ask Allah for forgiveness. (three times) </string>
    <string name="strings_azkar_translate36" translatable="false">O Allah, You are As-Salam and from You is all peace, blessed are You, O Possessor of majesty and honour: AS-Salam: The One Who is free from all defects and deficiencies.</string>
    <string name="strings_azkar_translate37" translatable="false">None has the right to be worshipped except Allah, alone, without partner, to Him belongs all sovereignty and praise and He is over all things omnipotent.O Allah, none can prevent what You have willed to bestow and none can bestow what You have willed to prevent, and no wealth or majesty can benefit anyone, as from You is all wealth and majesty.</string>
    <string name="strings_azkar_translate38" translatable="false">None has the right to be worshipped except Allah, alone, without partner, to Him belongs all sovereignty and praise and He is over all things omnipotent. There is no might nor power except with Allah, none has the right to be worshipped except Allah and we worship none except Him. For Him is all favour, grace, and glorious praise. None has the right to be worshipped except Allah and we are sincere in faith and devotion to Him although the disbelievers detest it.</string>
    <string name="strings_azkar_translate39" translatable="false">How perfect Allah is, all praise is for Allah, and Allah is the greatest. (thirty-three times)</string>
    <string name="strings_azkar_translate40" translatable="false">None has the right to be worshipped except Allah, alone, without partner, to Him belongs all sovereignty and praise and He is over all things omnipotent.</string>
    <string name="strings_azkar_translate41" translatable="false">(After morning and evening prayers, 3 times. After the other prayers 1 time.) </string>
    <string name="strings_azkar_translate42" translatable="false">{Allahu la ilaha illa huwa alhayyu alqayyoomu la ta/khuthuhu sinatun wala nawm...} [Al-Baqarah:255]</string>
    <string name="strings_azkar_translate43" translatable="false">None has the right to be worshipped except Allah, alone, without partner, to Him belongs all sovereignty and praise, He gives life and causes death and He is over all things omnipotent. (ten times after the maghrib and fajr prayers)</string>
    <string name="strings_azkar_translate44" translatable="false">O Allah, I ask You for knowledge which is beneficial and sustenance which is good, and deeds which are acceptable. (To be said after giving salam for the fajr prayer)</string>

    <string name="strings_azkar_translate45" translatable="false">In Your name my Lord, I lie down and in Your name I rise, so if You should take my soul then have mercy upon it, and if You should return my soul then protect it in the manner You do so with Your righteous servants.</string>
    <string name="strings_azkar_translate46" translatable="false">O Allah, verily You have created my soul and You shall take its life, to You belongs its life and death. If You should keep my soul alive then protect it, and if You should take its life then forgive it. O Allah, I ask You to grant me good health.</string>
    <string name="strings_azkar_translate47" translatable="false">O Allah, protect me from Your punishment on the day Your servants are resurrected. (three times)</string>
    <string name="strings_azkar_translate48" translatable="false">In Your name O Allah, I live and die.</string>
    <string name="strings_azkar_translate49" translatable="false">All praise is for Allah, Who fed us and gave us drink, and Who is sufficient for us and has sheltered us, for how many have none to suffice them or shelter them.</string>
    <string name="strings_azkar_translate50" translatable="false">O Allah, Knower of the seen and the unseen, Creator of the heavens and the earth, Lord and Sovereign of all things I bear witness that none has the right to be worshipped except You. I take refuge in You from the evil of my soul and from the evil and shirk of the devil, and from committing wrong against my soul or bringing such upon another Muslim: shirk: to associate others with Allah in those things which are specific to Him. This can occur in (1) belief, e.g. to believe that other than Allah has the power to benefit or harm, (2) speech, e.g. to swear by other than Allah and (3) action, e.g. to bow or prostrate to other than Allah.</string>
    <string name="strings_azkar_translate51" translatable="false">O Allah, I submit my soul unto You, and I entrust my affair unto You, and I turn my face towards You, and I totally rely on You, in hope and fear of You. Verily there is no refuge nor safe haven from You except with You. I believe in Your Book which You have revealed and in Your Prophet whom You have sent.</string>
</resources>